SURELY TOMORROW
Be honest with me. Have you ever rented
a whole amusement park before?
I think I could rent it if I tried.
Just kidding. It was so much fun.
-You're going to work now.
-Okay.
You have a long way to go.
You must be tired.
At least there's no traffic.
I'm going to order some food.
Want to join me?
I knew something was missing.
There were no snacks at the park.
Right. I knew something was missing too.
It's not easy to have
only one serving delivered.
You're right. And the good places
always have the minimum order.
Right.
Are you coming?
Sure.
SURELY TOMORROW
EPISODE 6
-Who is it?
-What?
What? Let me see.
It's just work.
What is it? Show me.
You're embarrassing me.
-Fine. So mean.
-Watch the movie.
Hey.
What?
Aren't you going to work?
Good morning.
Sure, it's a good morning.
Wash up and go make money.
Okay.
Jeez.
Use the bathroom in the master bedroom.
That one's broken.
Okay.
Have you seen my clothes?
-I have.
-I'm late.
Shit.
I saw it all when I put the patch on you.
Why are you shy now?
Don't talk to me. I can't multitask.
Good morning.
Well.
You're wearing the same clothes,
but you look neat.
Well, my parents
run the laundromat after all.
Did someone iron it for you?
Why are you so early today--
We need to talk.
Good morning.
Assistant Manager, good morning.
Is it?
What's wrong with him?
Don't you have a brain?
How can I live then?
When you met with the general manager…
Are you out of your mind?
You're backing out
of the overseas training? Why?
There's something I have to do.
Don't you know others are desperate to go?
We pay for the tuition and the housing.
Why would you refuse to go?
You can't let this go. We didn't accept
applications from your level.
You're right.
I'm sure I'll regret it very much later.
But?
This thing that I have to do
can only be done now.
I've given it a lot of thought.
I know I'll regret it later
that I didn't go to Chicago, but…
if I don't get this sorted out now,
I'll be messed up for the rest of my life.
Is it Seo Ji-woo again?
I got scared
now that I was about to leave.
I have traveler's diarrhea,
and a sensitive stomach.
When you were assigned to Current Affairs,
Seo Ji-woo got in your way.
She disappeared,
and you drowned yourself in booze.
And you're giving up overseas training
that everyone's after? Again, you idiot?
That's not true.
I have an important plan.
Why does Seo Ji-woo have to ruin
every important moment of your life?
What does she mean to you
that you surrender every time?
You can't even plant the flag.
Don't you dare call that love.
Min-woo! Ta-da.
I'll stay quiet for a while,
and I'll start at my father's company.
How's your condition?
You mean drugs?
I should be a good son now.
Yeah, quit doing drugs
and come to my senses.
Apparently, I need to exercise a lot.
Then I heard you're here, so I came.
This place is nice and quiet.
Well, you know,
Seo Ji-woo has a man, you know?
That ass who was in the picture with her.
They say there's nothing,
but they're living together.
-Shit.
-Living together?
He said straight up
that he's flirting with her.
Min-woo, who the hell is he?
Ji-woo's living with a guy?
If that's what's happening,
I'm the only one defeated.
I feel like I fell for their trap.
Why do you care when you're divorced?
Just go on your way.
We could get back together.
-What?
-Whatever. That's up to me.
By the way, Min-woo, well,
An Da-hye keeps calling me.
Maybe because you keep picking up.
You know what she said?
She told me to tell you,
either answer the phone or pay a visit.
Why me?
That's what I mean.
Why would she want to talk to you?
Is it about the money she borrowed?
She said it was urgent,
so I lent her some.
It wasn't even that much. Why bother?
Give her a call. She's a pathetic girl.
FAMOUS COMEDIAN KIM U-JAE
FINED FOR FRAUD
Why does Seo Ji-woo have to ruin
every important moment of your life?
What does she mean to you
that you surrender every time?
You can't even put the flag.
Don't you dare call that love.
How's your schedule tomorrow? Can we meet?
INCOMING CALL
LEE KYEONG-DO
Hello?
Ms. Seo. This is Lee Kyeong-do.
You wanted to see me today.
Who?
Isn't this Ms. Seo Ji-yeon's phone?
Seo Ji-yeon?
I don't know who Seo Ji-yeon is.
Where are you? Where are you right now?
I'm at the company cafeteria. I'm eating.
Ms. Seo,
you said to have lunch together,
but you are eating alone?
I guess the food is pretty good today.
Ms. Seo, I think you're done.
The coffee's on me, okay?
All right. Shall we get going?
Why is the cafeteria so cold?
Do you want to put this on? It's okay.
We have a plan.
Now, get up. Get up slowly. Okay.
We have a meeting.
Do we go to the right or the left?
Right?
Ms. Seo, are you okay?
Yeah, right.
Can you get me a change of clothes?
Yes, ma'am. I'll prepare it right away.
Okay.
Get something warm for her.
I guess I can't hide it anymore, right?
I'm such a mess.
You should get some rest at home.
How's Ji-woo doing?
If you talk to her,
she'll soon start working.
That's great.
That's really great. I'm finally relieved.
Thank you.
I think you should talk to Ji-woo soon…
I should, but not now.
She has finally made up her mind.
If she finds out that I'm sick,
she might get scared.
But it won't take long.
My husband is
already looking for a nursing home
in Canada.
Are you saying he knows?
Then why…
I told you.
He's not exactly a good husband.
It's not even that surprising.
Ji-woo should start working soon.
This is ironic.
I…
I was actually the one
who split you two up at that time.
Ji-woo,
you can't be here.
Ji-yeon, but…
But Kyeong-do is all I have.
That's all the more reason
why you shouldn't be here.
The amusement park.
I can't stop thinking about it.
I don't remember the last time
I had that much fun.
This dinner is a thank you.
Fine dining is surely different.
It's delicious. Oh, I'm full.
Why are you laughing? I said it's good.
I was scared because of the prices.
You know I have the shirt trauma.
It's nice to see you eat
without complaining.
It's nice to have a good friend
who treats me like this.
Sure, you have a good friend.
A friend who can take me
to an amusement park at this age.
Good.
What exactly made you upset--
Just call me a female friend.
A friend who is female.
We were having a good time.
Stop nitpicking.
You said you had a question.
Ask your female friend.
I'm not going to if you act so grumpy.
Kyeong-do,
what are you so curious about?
My friend Lee Kyeong-do?
My goodness.
About back then.
Don't take it too seriously.
I just think about it sometimes,
and I'm curious.
Why are you beating around the bush?
Why…
did you leave me?
Back then in Yeonnam-dong.
Do you want to get out of here?
Let's go somewhere refreshing.
Remember how Cho Jin-eon came to my house?
The day you saw him.
He called me Cinderella after midnight.
He said even if I fight back,
only rats will surround me.
That fucking son of a bitch.
Back then,
when I left you,
I saw myself after midnight.
This Saturday…
SUMMER, 2015
…we're going to a fancy restaurant.
Really? What? Where?
I found a nice Korean restaurant.
Why? Is it some kind of an anniversary?
A day to have great food.
Great food…
Hey, Mom.
Dad? How serious?
Which hospital? Okay. Bye.
I have to go to the hospital.
My dad is badly injured.
Wait for me at home. I will--
You should get going. Hurry up.
Yeah, sorry. See you later.
MISSED CALLS
JI-YEON - MOM - DAD
OPERATING
He just needs to survive. Your dad.
As long as he survives.
That's all I ask for.
He'll be fine. Don't worry, Mom.
JI-WOO
Hey, Ji-woo.
Yeah, he… He's getting surgery.
Don't worry too much.
Don't skip any meals.
I think I'll have to stay here.
Yes, I'm fine.
Call me if you need anything.
I'll keep my phone on.
Okay.
Sleep with the lights on if you're scared.
Bye.
MOM
Hey.
How's your father?
The surgery went well,
but his fever is not getting any better.
We'll have to wait
until he becomes stabilized.
Okay.
Still, I'm glad to hear
that his surgery went well.
Yeah.
I have to go back.
Right. Sure. Okay.
Are you going to be okay?
Do you want to stay at Se-yeong's?
No, I want to stay here.
I'm okay by myself. Don't worry.
Sorry.
Why are you sorry?
Make sure your mother eats well.
Yeah, you also should eat well.
You look terrible.
Bye.
Ji-woo.
Hey…
I see…
I was Mom's hell.
I had no idea.
I simply wanted to know
if I was her real daughter.
Funny.
She hates the kid
she got from having an affair?
Are you okay with me?
Were you okay?
I think you were about eight…
when I found out.
I overheard Mom and Dad talking.
I put some tissue in your ears
when you were sleeping
so you wouldn't hear anything.
I didn't want you to hear it forever,
but I'm saying it with my own mouth.
Ji-woo,
you can't be here.
Ji-yeon, but…
But Kyeong-do is all I have.
That's all the more reason
why you shouldn't be here.
The look she gave you your whole life
and her horrible contempt.
All that will go to Kyeong-do.
That drives people crazy…
Ji-woo.
You must have a decent life.
Not as the daughter of an actor
who barely makes a living in Vienna,
but as the shining Seo Ji-woo of JARIM.
His father.
He's very badly injured.
It's serious.
Lee Kyeong-do can't afford
to look after you.
Doctor, the BP is dropping.
-Check again.
-Yes.
YEONNAM UNDERGROUND WALKWAY
That's all the more reason
why you shouldn't be here.
The look she gave you your whole life
and her horrible contempt.
All that will go to Kyeong-do.
Will you change the server in charge?
It'll be uncomfortable
when we're here to enjoy dinner.
A mere part-timer in a VIP room?
It doesn't sound right, does it?
Ji-woo, why is your phone off?
Ji-woo…
-Ji-woo--
-The phone is turned off. Please…
Ji-woo…
I got to enjoy a life of luxury thanks
to a good stepdad and a good sister.
But now I'm just…
Cinderella.
A sad ending.
At the time, I was too…
I mean, it's not that I left you…
but I left to die.
But it was really frightening to die.
Good job, Seo Ji-woo.
Thank you for surviving.
I mean it. Thank you so much.
Hey, why is that a good job?
You almost died.
I was doing just fine
and suddenly showed up divorced.
Why…
Why are you still so stupid?
So naive. You're way too kind.
I'm sorry.
This is crazy.
Why are you sorry?
When you were having the hardest time,
I wasn't there.
I wasn't there for you.
At the time,
my father was in a serious condition…
That wasn't on you.
That was on me.
I wasn't there for you
when you were struggling the most.
Did you cry a lot?
Did it hurt a lot?
You're a damn kind lunatic.
It's because…
I was too petty…
I thought you left…
because my place was too small.
Because my bed was too worn out.
Because the bathroom smelled like a sewer.
Because the slime in the sink
would never go away.
I thought… that's why you left.
Every time… every time I drank,
that's all I thought about.
You know those suffocating thoughts
with no exit?
I drank because that was so stupid of me.
I drank again after calling you an asshole
and a bitch.
I drank again…
because… I missed you.
So I drank.
Kyeong-do,
I hate the word shame.
I even hate how it sounds.
I hate how it keeps sticking to me.
When you're so close to me
and smile at me,
then it makes it so hard for me
to ask you to leave.
That's why I hate the word shame.
Ji-woo,
when I was 20 or even now,
I'm still clumsy.
I'm not sure about what I should do
to make you feel
comfortable.
Your sister seems very ill.
But don't be afraid.
I know I'm clumsy and sloppy,
but I'll do anything. Anything for you.
I got home easily thanks to you.
Aren't you tired?
It's not so tiring to drive a nice car.
-You need to call a taxi, right?
-Yes.
I have something to say.
I should've told you earlier,
but the timing wasn't right.
What is it?
Can I have a cup of tea?
Be calm.
As if it's nothing serious. Okay?
Damn it.
That's Ji-yeon's number.
I think it's best for me to tell Ji-woo.
You got a call.
Really?
You're not calling back?
Yeah, later. It's not urgent.
Lee Kyeong-do.
Why do you have to talk to my sister?
What do you need to tell me?
Ji-woo.
Yes, say it.
INCOMING CALL
JI-YEON
Hello?
Yes. Now?
No, I'll come.
Bye.
You'd better explain this.
I can explain.
We'll talk when I'm back.
Okay.
Are you angry?
Did I pick the wrong day?
Lee Kyeong-do's in my house.
Let's settle things face-to-face.
Ji-yeon, why…
Why are you in touch with him?
I guess you can,
but how come I didn't know?
Busted.
What's it about?
It might not be a big deal for you,
but I'm getting offended.
Lee Kyeong-do is such a consistent man.
When it comes to you,
he's always attentive.
What?
I asked him to stop you.
I told him the flight schedule and all.
Well, I told him just in case
because I was desperate,
but he dashed there right away.
Why is he… Seriously.
So? Did you tell him to coax me
into working at the company?
What?
No wonder he was being so diligent.
It was to make me quit drinking
before I start working.
My goodness.
You know what?
He moved into my house with his stuff.
Really?
He said
he's an alcoholism treatment expert.
That's putting too much pressure on me.
Get lost, you son of a bitch.
Don't even call yourself a human being.
How can you hide that from me?
Just get the hell out of my life,
you motherfucking fraud!
Damn it.
Was it funny?
I must've looked ridiculous
jumping around without a clue.
Here is the biggest butthead
in the world, Seo Ji-woo.
Why else would you have stopped me?
Will you leave?
Whether I drink or whatever,
get out of my life.
No.
No, stop.
Please stop!
You know how Dad
cherished this company so much?
I want to do well,
but I see the limit.
I guess I was only smart at school.
Right. You were damn smart at school.
But you're the one who likes fashion.
Yeah.
I want to get some rest now
and look after Ro-a.
You need to take over now.
Give me a break.
Ji-yeon, are you ill?
What?
It's just stress and a headache.
My head hurts a bit.
-I'm sorry.
-Why are you sorry?
Ji-yeon, I…
-I was born out of wedlock.
-Ji-woo.
No, listen to me.
I've always wanted to say this.
Because of my situation, I thought
I shouldn't even set foot in the company.
I've received love, support,
and cheer from Dad more than I deserved.
I'm thankful for that.
I really wouldn't ask for more.
I didn't know
how much you were struggling.
I'm sorry that I was being selfish.
I was actually about to tell you.
I'll start working.
Are you crying?
Are you touched?
Yes.
I'm already overwhelmed
just imagining us working together.
When I thought about it,
I had no reason to chicken out.
I have you.
I can't do it alone, but with you,
it wouldn't be so bad.
What do you mean?
I bet you'd give JARIM Apparel wings.
Ji-yeon said…
I'm sorry. I should've--
…that it was Kyeong-do's fatal first love
that stopped Ji-woo.
What?
Am I really your first love?
-Yeah.
-Nobody from middle school or high school?
Probably not.
Right. You wouldn't stop me
just because she asked.
You're a man of your own.
That's kind of true.
I've talked to Ji-yeon.
Okay…
When I said I'll start working,
she said it's like giving JARIM wings.
So what is it?
What do you have to tell me?
Well,
that you actually showed up at the airport
because Ji-yeon asked? Is it about that?
What?
Yeah.
What? Did you think
I'd be disappointed if I found out?
Well, it's rather
that she gave me an excuse to stop you.
It wasn't solely because she told me to.
That means Ji-yeon and you…
read each other's minds.
Just like that!
Hey, thanks a lot.
So Ji-yeon and you
both thought about me, right?
Hey, that's so touching.
Yeah, right.
INCOMING CALL
KIM DOO-JIN
Hey, Kyeong-do.
She is completely wasted.
Then you should've taken her home.
She won't budge
unless it's to take a drink.
Jeez.
Hey, Kyeong-do.
Did you do something wrong to her?
Why?
She wouldn't eat any food.
She kept murmuring your name
and clenched her teeth.
Whatever. We need to switch.
I feel like my back is going to break.
Sure. Good work.
I'll get a taxi for her. Get going.
Jeez… that reminds me.
Kyeong-do, are you not going to Chicago?
It ended up that way.
Wait, who told you?
Someone who said you deserved
to be beaten to death…
Bye.
Hey. Why are you involved with An Da-hye?
Gosh… Stop asking already.
There's nothing between me and her.
I've never even met her before!
That punk has an anger issue.
-Department Manager Jin.
-Yes.
Reporter Lee is here.
Will you please leave now?
Who called this damn jerk?
Why are you Dongwoon Daily idiots
making a fuss at my job?
I have an actor's photoshoot tomorrow.
What if I can't get sober before then?
She probably didn't force you.
I know you drank on your own.
Hey,
one easily leads to another and ten more.
It tastes damn good.
I'm sick of drinking.
When will I ever stop?
I'm leaving.
Hey, where are you going?
Good night.
Kim Doo-jin that punk. Shit.
Why did you come?
Ow, my head. Let's go.
-Let me get you a taxi.
-Thank you so fucking much.
Han-kyeong.
To me, Ji-woo is like
a thick photo album that's always open.
I can't add a new picture.
I can't remove
all the pictures inside, either.
Shit.
But Chicago is too good to lose.
I know. It is.
You bring up a photo album
in the world of AI?
Just write a damn poem!
Assistant manager with analog sentiment.
Are you looking down on poetry?
Is calling it analog looking down,
you idiot?
Get yourself your own taxi.
So rude. You're always fucking rude.
Why are you following me?
There's only one exit.
Just jump off.
Don't we need to summon
the board of directors?
It's in the former chairman's will.
It wouldn't cause a problem.
Still, we should ask for their opinions.
It'd probably upset them.
Why bother listening to their complaints?
What did Ji-woo say? Is she confident?
Not sure.
You know what?
When I joined this company,
I wasn't confident.
How many people could say
that they're confident?
I'm sure Ji-woo will do better than me.
If she doesn't know anything,
she can learn.
You can help her.
Of course I'll help her.
That's not a problem.
I had to ask Ji-woo many times.
It wasn't an easy decision for her.
I barely convinced her into it
when she refused.
Because I'm ill,
she made a big decision to join.
You know what people are like.
When you're forced,
you're not that energetic.
Things could even end badly.
Aren't you going to ask how I'm ill?
Are you not well?
When was your last medical checkup?
I'm just making a fuss.
I just said that to make Ji-woo feel bad.
Well, it's a relief, then.
But you don't look that healthy either.
Take it easy.
It's your health that matters,
not the company.
Yeah. Thanks.
-Intern?
-Yes?
Is a female friend
different than a friend?
-What?
-It's the same category, right?
Look. Let's say I met a friend
who is a woman.
And I want to tell her thanks.
"I'm lucky to have a friend like you."
That means "Thanks to you," right?
Yes.
Then she went,
"Why not just call me a female friend?"
and lost her temper.
Something got on her nerves.
Here's my analysis.
So, for your female acquaintance,
both friend and female friend
are not good.
If she's really interested in you,
a friend or a female friend,
either would be terrible.
Right.
You know this for sure. Why did you ask?
Are you awake now?
Did it show?
Here, take it.
Wait, this is Doo-jin's favorite, right?
I liked it first.
It helps when you feel drowsy.
Thank you.
I feel recharged.
Right?
INCOMING CALL
SE-YEONG
Hello?
A new job party?
But you didn't throw me one,
but you'd do it for Ji-woo?
You? I nursed you when you were sick.
You want me to go into detail?
Nope. What time?
Yes. Okay.
Does that mean
I have to see Seo Ji-woo again?
I guess I have no choice but to meet her.
If you become a director,
can I get clothes for free at your shop?
Let me ask my sister.
Hey! A director should be able to
do that much.
Probably? Maybe? Maybe not?
-Mom.
-Yes.
When are we having the cake?
Do you want it?
We don't know when Jeong-min will be here.
Let's put the candles.
Sure. Yes. Hurry.
Don't you dare put the candles, you jerks.
The birthday boy isn't here yet.
You're never on time.
Because he was overprotected.
Ji-woo, hi.
When will your beauty finally die down?
You're so bright
that I want to add eye drops.
Jeong-min, your lame phrases
are still the same.
We have a pure soul here.
You should raise him strong,
or he'd end up like Jeong-min.
-You--
-Hey, that was a little harsh.
Hey, I really appreciate
this little surprise for my birthday,
but why do you keep teasing me?
Is this for me?
But seriously, I get to laugh
thanks to my friends, you know?
Who celebrates my birthday now?
Not even my mom does.
Honestly, I cried a little this morning.
You know, seriously,
you're all I have.
It's for me.
What?
Today is about me.
It's to celebrate my new job.
It's one shot, two kills.
We can celebrate them both.
Wow, double happiness. Right?
Yes, we're perfect for each other, right?
Double.
It's not working. Cut it out.
I'll let you blow the candles. Go.
I appreciate it. It's been three years
since I haven't done it.
Your life is so pitiful.
You should try out
the matchmaking companies.
Ji-woo! It's a good day.
Do you have to say that?
Right. You even sent me Korean beef.
I should be nice to you.
What?
When?
-What is that reaction?
-Really?
Hey, you brought it over.
Dong-won, you're pretty old now.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Jeong-min
One more time!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Jeong-min
One, two, three!
Good job! All right. Birthday noogies.
Okay, birthday noogies!
Okay, that's enough!
What's it like among the executives?
They're probably not welcoming Seo Ji-woo.
They're not happy about it.
But then they're not hasty enough to show
that they don't like it.
They all worked for
the former chairman after all.
It looks like they agreed to respect it.
What can I say about this company?
It's like some kind of a clique.
They didn't gather to make money,
but to worship my father-in-law.
I find that very uncomfortable.
It's something you need to acknowledge.
They've worked with Chairman Seo
since they were young.
And Chairman Seo looked after them
as if they were his family.
Do you think you can conquer
this mountain of obstacles?
Now that Seo Ji-woo showed up?
I'm so thankful that she showed up.
She's entering the cave
to get eaten on her own.
There's no way she'd do well.
She'll either bring the company down,
or stay crushed in one corner.
That only gives us a better excuse.
Sell JARIM, seize a fortune,
and disassemble.
I bet everyone will be on our side then.
Director Kang, what year were you born?
Out of nowhere?
You look at least
ten years younger than I am.
You're starting to drop the honorifics.
Oh, my, excuse me.
I guess I relied on you too much.
I was getting too comfortable with you.
I'll watch out.
Trust begins from such minor things.
The former chairman had never dropped
the honorifics with us before.
You might think it's not a big deal,
but things like that create respect.
I still have a lot to learn.
Allow me to fill your glass.
DELUXE TAXI PRIVATE
Thank you.
Good night.
Jesus, that old fossil. Seriously.
Yeah. What was I going to say?
Increase the doses.
I'll prepare more drugs.
Yeah. Thanks for your work.
We need to end it soon
for us to move on, Dan-bi.
Don't make any mistakes.
You're in front of a children's academy.
Oh, you're right.
I was actually thinking about
visiting you at work.
I think I was being too edgy
about Ji-woo last time.
But don't take it wrong.
I'm just worried.
I'm not saying anything about you two.
I know that. Jeez.
What is it between you two exactly?
Are you friends? Is it a fling?
Or are you in a relationship again?
I don't want us to be just friends.
Then get back with her.
-I can't ask her.
-Why not?
Are you afraid of losing her completely
if you break up again?
No, that was in the past.
Now I understand
why Ji-woo had to leave me.
No matter what happens,
I wouldn't lose her.
Then why can't you ask her?
I'm worried
what Ji-woo thinks about me.
What if she thinks that I'm making a move
now that she's divorced?
I'm afraid
that she might have low self-esteem.
Jesus, come on.
You're the type who can't make soy sauce
because you're scared of maggots, idiot.
How come you never change?
You look like
you've been gossiping about me.
It was about him.
To my face.
Hey, time to go home now.
Dong-won needs to go to bed. Go now.
Let's go.
Oh, right.
Here.
What's this?
A gift for starting your job.
Who wraps a gift like this?
What's inside is what matters.
Wow…
You seemed to like walking barefoot.
These are to stimulate pressure points.
My general manager wears the same pair.
Hey, forget it.
You wear them.
They're the best for circulation.
You can't expect
a fashion company director to wear these.
Keep them under your desk and wear them.
Put them on when you're alone.
It'll get rid of your back pain.
Do you sell these?
Oh, there you go again.
Is this really the only gift
you could get for me on Earth?
From the bottom of your heart?
You think the design sucks?
You want me to draw something?
Forget it.
There should be no traffic
on the Yeongdongdaegyo Bridge, right?
The traffic is probably gone.
Right.
Still, thanks. I'll wear them.
Well,
it'll be painful when you first wear them.
But if you keep wearing them…
it'll get rid of the headache and…
And the back pain.
Yes, that one. Yeah.
Yeah.
-Bye.
-Yeah, bye.
Bye.
-Bye.
-Did you call the taxi?
-I…
I should.
Want me to drop you off
at the subway station?
Well… Sure.
Okay.
Bye.
Don't cross the Yeongdongdaegyo Bridge.
Stay in Gangbuk today.
SURELY TOMORROW
"APRIL BRIDE"
JARIM APPAREL SEO JI-WOO
GETS MARRIED
"Only if…
one could entreat Elder Wolha…
that we be born…
with fates exchanged in the next life,
over a thousand ri away, I will die…
and you live."
"Then… you shall know the depth…
of…
of my sorrow."
"My second proposal to you!"
What's this bullshit, a second proposal?
What does he take Ji-woo for?
Damn it.
Sell the company?
I'm worried
if Ji-woo could put up with all this.
I'm happy
that you're not going to Chicago.
You're taking it personally
because she's your ex.
My current girlfriend.
There's something
you need to know, Ji-woo.
Kyeong-do has always had
the highest priority.
Ji-woo, I'll find you a world
that you'll like.